President's Office Records, 1927-1981
University of Houston Libraries
- Subject Files (Box 1-50)
  - Business Administration, College of, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 19-20)
  - Business Administration, College of, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Business Administration, College of, 1974-1979 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Business Administration, College of, Complaints re: 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Byrd, James A. - Assistant to the President, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Calendars, 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Camp Wallace, Acquisition of, 1959-1977 (Box 7, Folder 26-28)
  - Camp Wallace - General Correspondence, 1960-1973 (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
  - Campaign Fund - Miscellaneous, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Campaign Fund - Miscellaneous, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
  - Campaign Fund - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Campaign Fund - Report CLOSED, 1936-1939 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Campus Planning, 1967-1970 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Cartwright, Reagan Attorney for UH, 1956-1969 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Casey, Bob U.S. Congress, 1959-1966 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Casey, Bob U.S. Congress, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Casey, Bob U.S. Congress, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Casey, Bob U.S. Congress, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Casey, Bob U.S. Congress, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Casey, Bob U.S. Congress, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Casey, Bob U.S. Congress, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Casey, Bob U.S. Congressman, 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Catalogs, 1961-1973 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Cato, Lamar Q., 1937-1949 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Center for Government-Education Relations, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Center for Human Resources, 1968-1974 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Center for Human Resources, 1974-1977 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Center for Integrative Studies, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Center for Research in Business and Economics, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Chair Endowed-Special Professors, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Chairmen, Departmental, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Chairmen, Departmental, 1961-1975 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Chairmen, Departmental, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Chapman Case Materials - Court, 1966-1971 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Chapman, Randall Douglas, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 32-34)
  - Charter, University of Houston, 1933-1945 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Chemical Engineering, Department of, 1958-1973 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Chemistry, Department of, 1969-1974 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Chief Executives of the University of Houston, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Children's University Center, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Christmas Fund - Custodians and Maids, 1961-1972 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Citizenship and Career Conference, 1957-1961 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Clear Lake Campus, University of Houston (Box 9-11)
    - Administration/Formation, 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Administration/Formation, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Administration/Formation, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Administration/Formation, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Administration/Formation, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 10-11)
    - Formation/Acquisition of Land, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Formation/Report, "CLGC Survey to Determine Course Loads and Course Needs, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Formation/Report, "Clear Lake Graduate Center 1970-1975," 1969 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Formation/Groundbreaking, September-October 1969 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Administrative Files, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Administrative Files, February-April 1972 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Administrative Files, Dedication, May 4, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Administrative Files, June-September 1972 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Administrative Files, November 1972 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Administrative Files, December 1972 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Advisory Committee for Upper Division, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Administrative Files, January-March 1973 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Administrative Files, April-May 1973 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Administrative Files, June-July 1973 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Administrative Files, August 1973 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Administrative Files, Sept.-Dec. 1973 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Coordinating Board Members, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Administrative Files, January-February 1974 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Administrative Files, March-April 1974 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Administrative Files, May 1974 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Administrative Files/Groundbreaking, March-May 1974 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Administrative Files, June-July 1974 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Administrative Files, August 1974 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Administrative Files, September 1974 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Administrative Files, October 1974 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Administrative Files, January-February 1975 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Administrative Files, March 1975 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Files, April-May 1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Administrative Files, June 1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Administrative Files, July 1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Administrative Files, July 1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Administrative Files, August 1975 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Administrative Files, September 1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Administrative Files, October-November 1975 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Administrative Files, December 1975 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Administrative Files, January-February 1976 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Administrative Files, March 1976 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Administrative Files, April-July 1976 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Administrative Files, August-September 1976 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Administrative Files, October-December 1976 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Administrative Files, January-February 1977 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Administration/Advisory Council, February-March 1977 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Administrative Files, March-April 1977 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Administrative Files, May-June 1977 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Administration/Bayou Building Dedication, June 17, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Administration/Campus Dedication, October 1976-July 1977 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Administrative Files, July-August 1977 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Administrative Files, September-December 1977 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Administrative Files, January-March 1978 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Administrative Files, April-May 1978 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Administrative Files, June-July 1978 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Administrative Files, August-October 1978 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Administration/Appropriation Requests, February 1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Administration/Food Service, May 1979 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Administration/Chancellor Alfred R. Neumann, November 1978-November 1979 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Administration/Facilities Planning & Construction, November 1978-November 1979 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Administration/Enrollment, December 1978-November 1979 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Administration/Honor Societies, February-Nov. 1979 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Administration/General Correspondence, October 1978-December 1979 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Administration/Dinner Party, The, September 1979-February 1980 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Administration/Vacation and Absences, November 1978-February 1980 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 12-14)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 15-17)
  - Commander, Allen - General Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Commander, Allen - General Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Commander, Allen - General Correspondence, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Commander, Allen - General Correspondence, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Commander, Allen - General Correspondence, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Commander, Dr. Allen, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Commencement (Box 11-13)
    - Committees, 1958-1970 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Honorariums, 1955-1977 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Marshal, 1955-1977 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Programs - 1960, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Programs - 1961, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Program, Spring 1962 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Program, Summer 1962 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Program, Spring 1963 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Program, Summer 1963 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Program, Spring 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Program, Summer 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Program, Spring 1965 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Program, Summer 1965 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Program, Spring 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Program, Summer 1966 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Program, Summer 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Program, Summer 1967 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Program, Spring 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Program, Summer 1968 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Program, Summer 1969 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Program, Spring 1969 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Program, Spring 1970 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Program, Summer 1970 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Program, Spring 1971 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Program, Summer 1971 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Program, Spring 1972 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Program, Summer 1972 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Program, Spring 1973 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Program, Summer 1973 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Program, Fall 1973 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Program, Spring 1974 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Program, Summer 1974 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Program, Spring 1975 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Program, Summer 1975 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Program, Spring 1976 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Program, Summer 1976 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Programs, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Programs, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Programs, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Regalia Notes, 1962-1974 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Speakers, 1959-1973 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Committees (Box 13-17)
    - Academic Affairs, University, 1962-1965 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Academic Honesty, 1965-1970 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Academic Membership and Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Academic Membership and Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Academic Membership and Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Administration and Counselors Workshop, 1962-1969 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Admissions Review, University, 1970-1973 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Admissions Review, University, 1971-1977 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Admissions, University, 1962-1971 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Admissions, University, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Admissions, University, 1973-1976 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Advisory, 1958-1961 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Allocations Faculty Development, Advisory, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Annual Conference on School and College Programs, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Art Selection, 1966-1973 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Athletic, University, 1969-1972 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Athletic, University, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Bates College of Law Dean, Advisory, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Building and Planning Committees and their Chairmen, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Central Campus, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 24-25)
    - Central Campus Athletic, 1973-1977 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Central Plant Expansion, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Centralized Animal Care Facility, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Child Care Center Advisory, 1973-1977 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Child Care Center Study Group, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Committee on Committees, 1962-1976 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Computer User Groups, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Contingency Fund, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Cooperative Scholarship and Counseling Program for Model Cities Disadvantaged Students, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Criminal Justice Programs, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Critical Issues Planning, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Director of Library (ad hoc), 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Disadvantaged Students, Advisory Board for, 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Drug Use, University, 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Education and Special Problems of Black Athletes, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Education, College of, Development, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Excellence, Committee for (ad hoc), 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Facilities Planning, 1972-1977 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Facilities Planning, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Faculty Development Leave, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Faculty Development Leave, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Faculty Development Leave, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Faculty Development Leave, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Faculty Development Leave, 1970-1973 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Faculty Development Leave, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Development Leave, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Development Leave, 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Development Leave, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 4-7)
    - Faculty Development Leave, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Development Leave, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 9-11)
    - Faculty Memorial Resolutions, 1958-1977 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Senate, 1972-1977 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Food Service Planning, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Football Halftime Program, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Full Funding of Education Programs, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Goals Inventory, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Governance, 1969-1971 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Governance, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Governance, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Graduate Dean Selection, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Grievance and Tenure (ad hoc), 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Handicapped Students, 1968-1971 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Institute for Urban Studies, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Institute for Urban Studies, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Institute for Urban Studies, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - International Student Problems, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Joint to Study University Goals, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Landscape Planning, 1968-1970 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Latin American Studies, 1965-1975 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Law Enforcement Training, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Legal Aid Clinic (ad hoc), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Legal Information Counselor, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Library Building Dedication, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Library, University, 1968-1970 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Library, University, 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Library, University, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Library, University, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Listening Post, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Loans and Scholarships, 1962-1966 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Loans and Scholarships, 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Loans and Scholarships, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Loans and Scholarships, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Loans and Scholarships, 1974-1977 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Management Information Systems, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Marine and Coastal Environment Council, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Orientation Steering, 1964-1974 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Peavy, Dr. Charles D., 1973 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Planning Engineering Building Exterior, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Pre-medical, 1962-1974 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Presidential Screening, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Presidential Study Group, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - President's Consultative, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Procedural System Special Hearing, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Project Planning UH/DC, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Publications, University, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Publications, University, 1968-1973 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Publications, University, 1974-1977 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Radiation Safety, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Radiation Safety, 1975-1977 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Release of Student Records Policy, 1970-1975 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Reorganization Study, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Reorganization Study, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 26-28)
    - Reorganization Study, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Research Task Force (ad hoc), 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Research, University, 1967-1970 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Research, University, 1971-1973 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Research, University, 1962-1973 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Research, University, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Research, University, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Research, University, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Review Committee on System Education Programs - Technology, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Science and Research Building Unit 2 Project, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Search Athletic Director, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Search Chief Financial Officer, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Search Dean College of Optometry, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Search Dean Graduate School of Social Work, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Search Director of Security, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Search Internal Auditor, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Search Provost Central Campus, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Self Study Steering, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Self Study Steering, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
    - Self Study Steering, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Self Study (Southern Association), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Self Study Steering (Southern Association), 1963 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Self Study Steering (Southern Association), 1964 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Self Study Steering (Southern Association), 1965 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Self Study Steering (Southern Association), 1966-1968 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Southern Association Visitation, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Southern Association Visitation, 1966-1968 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Space Allocation, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Staff Traffic Appeal Board, 1971-1976 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Standing Committee, University of Houston, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Student Academic Advisement, 1971-1974 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Student Development Research, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Student Publications, 1970-1974 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Student Publications, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Student Publications, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Student Publications, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Student Publications, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Student Publications, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Student Publications, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Student Services Fee Planning and Allocation, 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Student Service Fee, 1975-1977 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Teaching Loads, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Technology, College of (ad hoc), 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Technology Programming, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Technology Programs, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Television, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - University Council Governance, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - University Finance (ad hoc), 1974-1978 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - University Security Advisory Board, 1974-1977 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - University Standing, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 33-34)
    - Urban Public Universities, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 35-37)
    - Urban Public Universities, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 38-39)
    - Urban Public Universities, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Urban Public Universities, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Urban Program Universities, March to June 1978 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Urban Program Universities, July to December 1978 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Water Resources Research, 1966-1972 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Communication Arts Department, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Computer Center, 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Computer Center, 1970-1973 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Computer Center, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Computer Center, 1974-1978 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Conant, Ralph Director, Institute of Urban Studies, 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Congress of the United States Texas Delegation, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Connally, John, 1963-1976 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Constitutional Tax Bonds, 1968-1971 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Continuing Education, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Continuing Education, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Continuing Education, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Continuing Education, 1976-1979 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Continuing Education Center Dedication, 1969-1975 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Controller, 1975-1979 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Cooperative Education, 1975-1978 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Coordinating Council (Committee), 1973 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Coordinating Council (Committee), 1974-1976 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Coordinating Council-Calendar of Meetings, 1975-1978 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Coordinating Council-Committees, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Coordinating Council-General Correspondence 1972-1976 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Coordinating Council-Meeting, May 20, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Coordinating Council-Meeting, September 17, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Coordinating Council-Meeting, December 18, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Coordinating Council-Meeting, February 18, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Coordinating Council-Meeting, April 29, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Coordinating Council-Meeting, June 30, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Coordinating Council-Meeting, July 28, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Coordinating Council-Meeting, September 22, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Coordinating Council-Meeting, October 28, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Coordinating Council-Meeting, November 17, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Coordinating Council-Meeting, March 22, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Coordinating Council-Meeting, April 19, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Coordinating Council-Meeting, November 22, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Coordinating Council-Meeting, February 28, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Coordinating Council-Meeting, May 12, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Coordinating Council-Meeting, October 17, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Coordinating Council-Meeting, December 12, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Coordinating Council-Meeting, February 6, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Coordinating Council-Meeting, June 5, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Coordinating Council-Meeting, June 5, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Coordinating Council-Membership List, 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Coordinating Council-Policies, 1973-1976 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Coordinating Council-Policies, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Cougar, 1967-1974 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Cougar, 1974-1977 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Cougar Club, 1962-1976 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Council on Post-secondary Accreditation, 1975-1977 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Counseling and Testing, 1973-1976 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Counseling and Testing, 1975-1977 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Crackpots, 1966-1971 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Crackpots, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Crackpots, 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Crackpot, Two Individuals, 1951-1976 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Cresap, McCormick and Paget, 1968-1976 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Cullen Boulevard-Closing of, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Cullen Center Bank and Trust, 1969-1973 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Cullen, Ezekiel W. Portrait, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Cullen Foundation, 1950-1962 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Cullen Foundation, 1963-1966 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Cullen Foundation, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Cullen Foundation, 1964-1973 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Cullen, H. R. - Miscellaneous, 1939-1958 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Cullen, H. R. - Oil Royalty, 1945-1949 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Cullen, H. R. - Oil Royalty, 1950-1970 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Cullen, H. R. - Statements re: Financial Aid, 1951-1955 (Box 19, Folder 4)